His heart...
Why isn't it beating?
My father isn't dead.
If I can get his Stand back,
he'll come back to life.
Know that this power of yours
is called a Stand.
I have to go see her. Jolyne...
Jolyne Kujo.
I see.
So Hermes learned
about Stands
and the discs.
When Hermes inserted McQueen's memory disc
into him,
he came back to life.
He was resurrected.
We can bring your father back
if we get his discs!
What did you do with
the janitor's discs?
I put them somewhere safe.
I have both of them.
She says the guards would find them
during the strip searches.
We'll keep his Stand,
but I'll insert
his memory disc later.
McQueen's memory disc.
This disc contains information
on Whitesnake.
And maybe
I'll be able to learn more
about Dad's discs.
It's coming!
Quick, close the door!
I was just changing
the tractor tire!
I barely touched it!
Hurry!
Move it, get out of there!
Close the door!
Help me!
OK!
It's so heavy!
Pull harder! It's almost closed.
Come on, pull!
What are you doing?
I told you to pull!
It's not my arms.
Man!
I know.
It's me...
who wasn't pulling hard enough...
The weather is nice, as always.
Tell me, Charlotte,
what's going on?
Why were we called out here?
This afternoon,
two inmates disappeared
in the farm sector.
Really?
That doesn't bode well.
They couldn't have escaped.
They must have drowned in the swamps
or gotten bitten by a snake.
I think we need to form
a search party.
Why don't you mention
the possibility of an alligator?
A female alligator?
Who said that?
How can you say that?
I didn't eat them!
I'm innocent!
Anyway.
I called you here
to form a group of volunteers.
No money involved,
no reduced sentence either.
I'm asking you for the sake of honor.
Is any one of you volunteering?
Come on, Jolyne.
You just got out of the punitive ward.
Why put yourself through this on top of it?
Because you won't be going.
What?
Very well.
Five will be more than enough.
Head guard!
The inmates going to the farm
must wear this bracelet,
which will keep them from running away.
This is the Like a Virgin.
An invisible barrier.
If you tamper with it
or if it breaks,
it will explode.
Also, if you get more than 50 meters away
from me,
it will explode.
Wiping yourself without arms,
that's not easy.
Follow me.
Fifty meters?
Do we have to run?
Wait!
You'll each search on your own
starting from here.
Watch out for the bushes.
Alligators hang around
in the swamps.
They can't be here.
Why did you volunteer,
Jolyne?
Though it suits me just fine.
There are plenty of things
I want to talk to you about.
About the disc
and about Whitesnake.
Did you look at it?
McQueen's disc, I mean?
Yes, I took a look at it.
It gave me a horrible sensation.
Like a vile stench
was seeping into my brain.
 So you didn't notice, then.
 Notice what?
The images in that disc
contain clues about
Whitesnake's goal.
McQueen.
This disc suits you.
It's yours now.
Here's your Stand.
They're hidden in a tire
of one of the farm tractors?
Did you see several of them inside?
His goal is to collect discs.
He has a collection
of Stands and memories
stolen from other Stand users.
There are dozens of discs.
He must be hiding them
from the guards and the other inmates.
That's why
he hides them in a tire.
The discs containing
my father's Stand, Star Platinum,
and his memory must be there.
What? Your father?
So you're searching
for your father's discs.
Sorry, I don't know any more about him.
I'll go look for the disc's tractor.
A tractor?
There are tons of them here.
 That barn.
 Yes.
Hey, you two! Having fun?
You think this is a picnic?
You're not searching at all!
No, we were talking about that barn.
We'll go search over there.
You made us chase after you on purpose.
Who's having fun now, huh?
Wait! What are you mumbling?
Nothing at all.
I promised myself I'd run around
like a bitch in heat.
How vulgar.
Alligator dung.
I told you to wait!
You insolent little slut!
I'm the head guard!
Oops. That was an accident.
The baton accidentally brushed
against the bracelet.
What's that ringing?
Why is my bracelet ringing?
I didn't do it on purpose.
You charged at me.
It's not going to explode, is it?
This is a sick joke.
Do something!
Hey, stay away from me.
It might explode
while you're too close to me.
Hold on a second.
I said I was sorry!
I apologize!
Watch it! I told you to stay away from me.
Arrest this...
Serves you right!
Go eat
alligator crap!
 It stopped.
 Don't panic, Hermes.
That ringing was just a warning.
Right, guard?
Good freaking grief.
So that's what your power was.
Come on.
There's nothing here but tractors
and sacks of flour.
No point searching inside.
If this had been an easy mission,
they wouldn't have needed volunteers.
Seriously?
It's here, Jolyne!
It's the tractor.
The same tractor as in the disc.
With the same number.
Same model, same number. Number four.
They're in that tire.
We'll find the discs
by taking the tire off.
Open your ears!
We're going to comb the swamps.
The missing ones may have drowned.
Search for them.
What does he think? That we're going for a swim?
I'm not going.
Let's go!
That's not an option.
Get off our backs.
We could catch some nasty crap
in these swamps!
What a drag.
It's now or never.
Let's take the tire off!
Jolyne...
Something's off.
Yeah, something's really wrong.
I know. If we don't take the tire off
right now,
we'll be too far from the guard.
No, that's not what I mean.
He said: "Five will be more than enough."
The guard.
He said five inmates would be enough.
But there are six of us!
Jolyne, what does that mean?
Counting you and me,
that makes six!
I know we were five
when we left.
But I didn't pay attention
to their clothes or their hairstyles.
What do you think, Jolyne?
I don't know.
I was busy catching up with you.
That said, everyone's wearing a bracelet.
It's strange.
Have we been six
from the start?
You find it weird too, don't you?
We should be five, right?
Do you know who joined us?
No, I could be wrong.
Besides, our numbers hardly matter.
She's been with me since the start.
I remember her.
Her name is Atroe.
She gets picked on a lot.
She volunteered
to get away from her bullies.
Right?
I don't know you.
What?
What's going on?
Why is my bracelet ringing?
Mine too!
 Mine too.
 Damn it, they're all ringing!
We must be getting close
to the 50-meter limit.
But he can't be that far away.
The guard is gone!
Where did he go?
The quad is covered in blood.
But why?
Our bracelets are still ringing,
the guard's body is moving away from us.
Did he drown?
Is his body being carried away?
Find the guard!
He must be within 50 meters!
This sucks!
Hey!
My bracelet's ringing is speeding up.
Not this.
 She's dead.
 No, not this.
The sixth one must be
attacking us.
Because we got close
to the discs?
Let's search for the guard within a 50-meter
circle around her.
There he is!
Get closer to him!
Our bracelets will stop ringing
and won't explode.
Don't let your guard down, Jolyne.
Our enemy is in this group.
There's a real psycho in here.
She looks suspicious.
The short-haired one.
And Atroe didn't recognize her.
It must be her.
Her Stand must have killed the guard.
We'll kill her before she kills us.
Calm down, Hermes.
Assuming she's our enemy,
she must have been watching the discs
without interruption.
 That would make sense.
 That's impossible.
She's an inmate here.
An inmate can't watch
the discs around the clock.
Jolyne, get back!
 There's something there!
 What?
Get back.
Get out of the water!
Hermes.
 Did you see something?
 No.
It was nothing.
But let's get out of these swamps.
By the way, Jolyne.
We must not split up,
no matter what.
We don't know who our enemy is.
Yes. And these bracelets
make things harder.
Before we can retrieve the discs,
we need to be within 50 meters
of the guard and the three other inmates.
Hermes!
There's something in the bucket!
My head got sucked in!
What is this plankton-like thing?
What?
It split in two.
No, in four!
These creatures...
The bucket wasn't empty.
I didn't look carefully enough.
They were already in the water.
Kiss!
Hermes!
Jolyne, don't move.
The water is dangerous!
These things multiply!
They multiply very fast.
Get out of the water.
You won't make it in time.
The Stand set a trap for me.
Stone Free!
I'll get him.
Jolyne.
You're walking on a thread.
Are you unraveling your own body?
Jolyne, stay back.
I can handle this on my own!
That's crazy!
Yeah.
It's crazy all right.
Damn it.
I would've been done for
if I hadn't unraveled so much thread.
So that's your power.
There's a hole in your body.
She let it hit her
so she could latch onto it.
Jolyne, get out of the water now.
Don't just stand there, Hermes!
This thing.
Its shape comes from the plankton.
It was hiding in the little water
there was in the bucket.
That's what dragged me under.
I know all that.
So don't just stand there.
Grab it underwater.
The thread I unraveled.
Powerful and fast!
But what's going on?
A Stand's power must weaken
when its user moves away from it.
It got me.
Stay calm, Jolyne.
I stuck a sticker on him
while latching onto his arm.
That's my power.
I'll show you.
Quick, away from the water!
It's not chasing us.
It only attacks when it's in the water.
Answer me!
This is inmate FE32125.
This is an emergency.
The guard had an accident.
Send help immediately.
What happened
to you two?
Did you run on water?
You three, don't move!
Don't go near the water!
Don't even try to play tricks on us.
I know one of you
did this to us!
Before I retrieve the disc,
I must find out who its user is.